# Sai Bharathi Korupolu

Full Stack Developer

Dedicated and efficient full stack developer with 3 years of experience in presentation layers, application layers, and databases. Proficient in creating user interfaces, writing and testing codes, troubleshooting simple/complex issues, and implementing new features based on user feedback. Seeking to further improve my MERN skills for developing my career and for the growth of the organization.

#### $\times$

bharathi.korupolu@gmail.co m

П

9573281150



Visakhapatnam, India



goofy-jones-90c5d2.netlify.app

#### in

linkedin.com/in/sai-bharathikorupolu-495793164

## **SKILLS**

React.js

Node.js

Java

Oracle SQL

JavaScript

Express.js

MongoDB

HTML

CSS

JSON

GIT

XML

Tortoise SVN

Eclipse

iReport

VSCode

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Systems Engineer Infosys Limited

06/2018 - Present Chennai,TN

CLIENTS: China Trust Commercial Bank, Al Ahli Bank of Kuwait, Indigenous Business Australia, Australian Military Bank

Roles & Responsibilities

- Responsible to get the business requirements from Leads and Managers. Discuss in the scrum calls to have the design. Develop web applications using Node.js, Express.js, React.js and MongoDB (MERN stack).
- I am involved in creating proof of concepts to create a user interface and thus evaluating their feasibility and integration in the existing applications.
- Responsible for parsing JSON data to and from the server for presentation and storage purposes in the project.
- Used React Axios to call Web APIs to fetch data from backend and update the states in the store of Redux.
- Involved in all the stages of Software Development Life Cycle like Application Design, Development, Debugging and Testing all applications following Agile methodology.

## **INTERNSHIPS**

#### Indian Institute of Technology , Kharagpur (05/2017 - 07/2017)

'Ship design and Dynamics' under Dr.Viswanath Nagarajan, Department of Naval Architecture and Ocean Engineering.

## Hindustan Shipyard Limited (12/2016 - 01/2017)

Industrial training in design and all shipbuilding departments like Hull shop, Prefabrication shop, Erection.

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

My Portfolio (05/2020 - Present)

 Developed portfolio page and have been updating my works and skills on it. Please do visit my portfolio website (https://goofy-jones-90c5d2.netlify.app)

# **LANGUAGES**

## English

Full Professional Proficiency

#### Telugu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### Hindi

Limited Working Proficiency

#### Tamil

Elementary Proficiency

## **INTERESTS**

**Problem Solving** 

Singing

Badminton

Gardening

## **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Technology

Andhra University - Vishakapatnam

2014 - 2018 8.58

## Intermediate

Sri Chaitanya Junior College

2012 - 2014 96.8

## **High School**

Amar Concept School

2012 9.7

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### The Grand Slam Kudos Award

Appreciation Award for the category 'Rookie of the Team' for excellent performance

Best Outgoing Student Award - Andhra University (05/2018)